Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
8094
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-
600 cubic feet.
Vinyl records and other A/V Recordings, Financial Records, Manuscripts, Memorabilia, Photocopies, Photographs, Printed Materials, Publications.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Afrika Bambaataa is an American disc jockey, singer, and songwriter from the South Bronx, New York. Often called the “Godfather” of Hip Hop, Bambaataa has helped to define Hip Hop since it emerged in the South Bronx in the 1970s. One of a handful of Hip Hop's 1970s originators, Bambaataa gave Hip Hop its name, and was the first to define its core artistic elements - DJing, rapping, break dancing, and graffiti art - under one cultural umbrella. His cultural organization, the Universal Zulu Nation, has helped to spread Hip Hop culture throughout the world. His genre-defining 1982 song "Planet Rock" and subsequent electro-funk tracks have become icons of hip-hop and electronic music. In 2007 he was nominated for induction into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-; Universal Zulu Nation (Organization)
Subjects:
African American youth -- Social life and customs.; Disc jockeys.; Electronic music.; Funk (Music).; Hip-hop.; Hip-hop -- Influence.; Hip-hop -- History. -- United States; Music -- Social aspects.; Race relations.; Rap (Music); Rap (Music) -- Political aspects.; Rap musicians.; Hip-hop -- New York.; Rap (Music) -- New York.; Hip-hop; Rap (Music); Rap musicians; Social history
Places:
Bronx (New York, N.Y.) -- Social conditions -- 20th century.; New York (State) -- New York; New York (State) -- Bronx; United States
Form and Genre Terms:
History
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to collection restricted until completion of processing, with the exception of vinyl records that have been individually cataloged.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Manuscripts
a. School Papers and Assignments
b. Africa Trip
c. Soul Scrapbooks and Music Writing
d. Notebooks and Miscellaneous Manuscripts
e. Lyrics and Poems
f. Bronx River Neighborhood Center
g. Phone and Contact Lists
Series II. Flyers
Series III. Photographs
Series IV. Personal Papers
a. Personal Papers
b. Press About Bambaataa
c. Catalogs and Mail
Series V. Universal Zulu Nation Documents
a. Infinity Lessons
b. Administration
Series VI. Stage Costumes and Clothing
Series VII. Periodicals and Publications
a. Small Press Publications
b. Periodicals
c. Publications from 3410 De Reimer Ave. Bronx, NY
d. Other Publications
Series VIII. Moving images and audio recordings
a. Video cassettes
a. Audio cassettes
Series IX. Music collection
12 inch vinyl
Sureshots and altered/obscured
Numbered by Bambaataa
Annotated, not numbered (Alphabetical by artist)
A-D
E-H
I-L
L-O
P-S
T-Z
Numbers, unknown and various
Second alpha sequence
Cataloged individually
Not annotated (Alphabetical by artist)
A
B
C
D
E
F
G
H
I
J
K
L
M
N
O
P
Q
R
S
Afrika Bambaataa recordings
Renegades of Rhythm Tour
Test pressings and white labels (not yet cataloged)
Compilations (not yet cataloged)
7 inch vinyl
Numbered (not yet cataloged)
Annotated not numbered (not yet cataloged)
No annotations (not yet cataloged)
Acetates and lacquer discs
Cassettes (not yet cataloged)
CDs (not yet cataloged)
Series X. Ephemera
CONTAINER LIST
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Annotated, not numbered
      - I-L
        - I-Roy - Crisus time, 1976; SR-26626; I-Roy (Box 39)
          Catalog # CA 2011; A-side Matrix # CA 2011 A1
          Caroline Records
          New York, New York
        - I-Roy - The best of I-Roy, 1977; SR-26627; I-Roy (Box 39)
          Catalog # GG 007; A-side Matrix # DSR 4160
          GG's Records
          Jamaica
        - I Start Counting - My translucent hands no III, 1987; SR-26628; I Start Counting (Box 39)
          Catalog # 12 Mute 54; A-side Matrix # 12-MUTE-54A1
          Mute
          London, United Kingdom
        - Ice - Back to basics 2, 1996; SR-26629; Ice; DJ Ice (Box 39)
          In same jacket as # SR-26630. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 42333; A-side Matrix # 42333-THIS SIDE A
          Metro II Records
          Baltimore, Maryland
        - Ice - Back to basics 2, 1996; SR-26630; Ice; DJ Ice (Box 39)
          In same jacket as # SR-26629. 2 copies.
        - Ice Cube - AmeriKKKa's most wanted, 1990; SR-26631; Ice Cube (Box 39)
          Catalog # SL57120; A-side Matrix # SL-57120-A
          Priority Records
          Hollywood, California
        - Ice Cube - Greatest hits (Disc one), 2001; SR-26632; Ice Cube (Box 39)
          In same jacket as # SR-26633. Double album.
          Catalog # 7243 5 29091 1 7; A-side Matrix # 72435-29091-1-7-A S-48203
          Los Angeles, California
        - Ice Cube - Greatest hits (Disc two), 2001; SR-26633; Ice Cube (Box 39)
          In same jacket as # SR-26632. Double album.
          Catalog # 7243 5 29091 1 7; A-side Matrix # 72435-29091-1 7 C S-48205
        - Ice-T - Gotta lotta love, 1993; SR-26634; Ice-T (Box 39)
          In same jacket as # SR-26635. Different discs.
          Catalog # SPRO 6655; A-side Matrix # PVL 53821-A-21 S-27441
          Rhyme Syndicate Records
        - Ice-T - Gotta lotta love, 1993; SR-26635; Ice-T (Box 39)
          In same jacket as # SR-26634. Different discs.
          Catalog # 0-40737; A-side Matrix # 0-40737-A RE-1
          Sire
        - Ice-T - Killers; Body rock, 1985; SR-26636; Ice-T (Box 39)
          Catalog # EB002; A-side Matrix # EB 002-A
          Electrobeat Records
          San Pedro, California
        - Ijahman - Are we a warrior, 1979; SR-26637; Ijahman (Box 39)
          Catalog # MLPS-9557; A-side Matrix # MLPS-9557-A
          Mango Records
        - Ill Squad Production - On a roll; Making a killing, 1988; SR-26638; Ill Squad Production (Box 39)
          Catalog # WAR-024; A-side Matrix # WAR-024-TONY-1(RECUT)
          Idlers
          Brooklyn, New York
        - Ilusion - I like it loud, 1986; SR-26639; Ilusion (Box 39)
          Catalog # GHS 24108; A-side Matrix # GHS-24108-A-SR-2
          Geffen Records
        - Imagination - In the heat of the night, 1980; SR-26640; Imagination (Box 39)
          In same jacket as # SR-26641. 2 copies.
          Catalog # MCA-5373; A-side Matrix # MCA-3203-W1
          MCA Records
          Universal City, California
        - Imagination - In the heat of the night, 1980; SR-26641; Imagination (Box 39)
          In same jacket as # SR-26640. 2 copies.
        - Impact - The pac is back, 1977; SR-26642; Impact (Box 39)
          Test pressing
          Catalog # F-9539; A-side Matrix # F-9539-A
          Fantasy
          Berkeley, California
        - Cecil Holmes Souldful Sounds - The Black motion picture experience, 1973; SR-26643; Cecil Holmes Souldful Sounds (Box 39)
          In same jacket as # SR-26644. Different discs.
          Catalog # BDS 5129; A-side Matrix # BDS-5129-A
          Buddah Records
        - Impressions - The preacher man, 1973; SR-26644; Impressions (Box 39)
          In same jacket as # SR-26643. Different discs.
          Catalog # CRS 8016; A-side Matrix # CRS-8016-A
          Curtom
        - Impressions - Times have changed, 1972; SR-26645; Impressions (Box 39)
          Catalog # CRS 8012; A-side Matrix # CRS-8012-A
        - Ivy Queen - In the zone, 1998; SR-26646; Ivy Queen; Wyclef Jean; Omar Navarro; Deborah Castillero (Box 39)
          Catalog # EPDJ-82931; A-side Matrix # EPDJ-82931-A
          Sony Discos Dance
          Miami, Florida
        - In Time - People, 1990; SR-26647; In Time (Box 39)
          Catalog # COOLXW 217; A-side Matrix # COOLXW 217 A-1J-1-1
          Cooltempo
        - Independent Movement - Slippin' away, 1978; SR-26648; Independent Movement (Box 39)
          Catalog # PD-1-6152; A-side Matrix # PD-1-6152-AS-PW
          Polydor
        - Infamous DukeyMan - Hear the drummer, 1996; SR-26649; Infamous DukeyMan (Box 39)
          Catalog # KH1; A-side Matrix # KH-01-A
          Knucklehead Records
        - Information Society - Information Society, 1988; SR-26650; Information Society (Box 39)
          Catalog # TBLP 25691; A-side Matrix # 1-25691-A-SR1
          Tommy Boy
        - Ingram - D.J.'s delight, 1983; SR-26651; Ingram (Box 39)
          Catalog # DMD 399; A-side Matrix # ST-DMD-44023-2
          Mirage
        - Ingram, James - It's your night, 1983; SR-26652; Ingram, James (Box 39)
          Catalog # 1-23970; A-side Matrix # 1-2-3970-A-SH2 B-18588-SH2
          Qwest Records
        - Inner Circle - Everything is great, 1979; SR-26653; Inner Circle (Box 39)
          Catalog # ILPS 9558; A-side Matrix # ILPS-1-9558-REI-LW2
          Island Records
          Burbank, California
        - Inner Life - (Knock out) let's go another round, 1981; SR-26654; Inner Life (Box 39)
          Catalog # SG 354 (DJ); A-side Matrix # SG-354-A
          Salsoul Records
        - Inner Life - I'm caught up (in a one night love affair), 1979; SR-26655; Inner Life (Box 39)
          Catalog # PRL D 519; A-side Matrix # TD201A
          Prelude Records
        - Inner Thumb - Citroens 'n' sitars, 1999; SR-26656; Inner Thumb (Box 39)
          Catalog # EMN 10; A-side Matrix # OASIS DISC MASTERING EMN 10
          Emperor Norton
        - Instant Funk - Instant Funk, 1979; SR-26657; Instant Funk (Box 40)
          Catalog # SA 8513; A-side Matrix # SA-8513-A-11
        - Instant Funk - The funk is on, 1980; SR-26658; Instant Funk (Box 40)
          Catalog # SA 8536; A-side Matrix # SA-8536A
        - Instant Funk - Instant funk V, 1983; SR-26659; Instant Funk (Box 40)
          Catalog # SA 8558; A-side Matrix # SA-8558-A
        - Instant Funk - Why don't you think about me; Slam dunk the funk, 1982; SR-26660; Instant Funk (Box 40)
          In same jacket as # SR-26661. Different discs.
          Catalog # SG 365 DJ; A-side Matrix # SG-365-A
        - Instant Funk - Looks so fine, 1982; SR-26661; Instant Funk (Box 40)
          In same jacket as # SR-26660. Different discs.
          Catalog # SA 8545; A-side Matrix # SA-8545-A
        - Instant Funk - Witch doctor (Disc one), 1979; SR-26662; Instant Funk (Box 40)
          In same jacket as # SR-26663. Double album.
          Catalog # SA 8529-DJ; A-side Matrix # SA-8529-C-DJ-1
        - Instant Funk - Witch doctor (Disc two), 1979; SR-26663; Instant Funk (Box 40)
          In same jacket as # SR-26662. Double album.
          Catalog # SA 8529-DJ; A-side Matrix # SA-8529-E-DJ-1
        - Intelligent Concept - We're rockin' the planet, 1997; SR-26664; Intelligent Concept (Box 40)
          Catalog # OVER-X-PO 07; A-side Matrix # OVER-X-8007 A
          Over-X-Posure
          Hessen, Germany
        - Intimate Strangers - Raise the dragon, 1987; SR-26665; Intimate Strangers (Box 40)
          Catalog # IRS-23703; A-side Matrix # IRS 6272 AM5
          I.R.S. Records
        - Intruders - When we get married, 1970; SR-26666; Intruders (Box 40)
          Catalog # LPSG 5008; A-side Matrix # LTSG008A
          Gamble
        - Invisible Man's Band - X-country (flamin' hot), 1980; SR-26667; Invisible Man's Band (Box 40)
          Catalog # MLPS 7785; A-side Matrix # MLPS-7785-A CP2
          Mango
        - Invisibles - Donkey Kong (catch you in the break), 1984; SR-26668; Invisibles (Box 40)
          Catalog # JGMD-8196; A-side Matrix # JGMD-8196-A
          Dubwise Records
          Opa-Locka, Florida
        - INXS - Listen like thieves, 1985; SR-26669; INXS (Box 40)
          Catalog # 81277-1; A-side Matrix # ST-A-855781-B 1-1
          Atlantic
        - I.O.S. - Boom pop bang, 1997; SR-26670; I.O.S. (Box 40)
          Catalog # ET 002; A-side Matrix # BMC-6802A
          F.A.C.T. Records
          Detroit, Michigan
        - Irie, Tippa - It's good to have the feeling you're the best, 1984; SR-26671; Irie, Tippa (Box 40)
          Catalog # UKMC 4; A-side Matrix # UKMC-4 A
          UK Bubblers
        - Irie, Welton - Army life, 1982; SR-26672; Irie, Welton (Box 40)
          Catalog # DSR 5821; A-side Matrix # DSR 5821-A SPIDERMAN
          Dynamite
          Kingston, Jamaica
        - Isaacs, Gregory - Night nurse, 1982; SR-26673; Isaacs, Gregory (Box 40)
          In same jacket as # SR-26674. 2 copies.
          Catalog # MLPS 7798; A-side Matrix # MLPS-7798-A-CP3
        - Isaacs, Gregory - Night nurse, 1982; SR-26674; Isaacs, Gregory (Box 40)
          In same jacket as # SR-26673. 2 copies.
        - Isaacs, Gregory - Night nurse, 1982; SR-26675; Isaacs, Gregory (Box 40)
          Catalog # MLPS 9721; A-side Matrix # MLPS-9721-A
        - Ish - Ish, 1979; SR-26676; Ish (Box 40)
          Catalog # CL-8808; A-side Matrix # CL-8808-A-AM
          Clouds
        - Isle Natividad - #27 puffton; Extol, 2003; SR-26677; Isle Natividad (Box 40)
          In same jacket as # SR-26678. 2 copies.
          Catalog # Zone 060; A-side Matrix # Zone060-A
          Zone Records
          Orlando, Florida
        - Isle Natividad - #27 puffton; Extol, 2003; SR-26678; Isle Natividad (Box 40)
          In same jacket as # SR-26677. 2 copies.
        - Isle Natividad - Lonely; 2 to the 3, 2001; SR-26679; Isle Natividad (Box 40)
          Catalog # SW018; A-side Matrix # SW018-A
          Sweet Records
        - Isle Natividad - Give me your love, 1997; SR-26680; Isle Natividad (Box 40)
          Catalog # SW 008; A-side Matrix # SWEET 008-A
        - Isley Brothers - Inside you, 1981; SR-26681; Isley Brothers (Box 40)
          Catalog # FZ 37533; A-side Matrix # AL 37533-1B
          T-Neck
          New Jersey
        - Isley Brothers - It's alright with me, 1982; SR-26682; Isley Brothers (Box 40)
          Catalog # 4Z9-03282; A-side Matrix # 4Z9-03282-3AA
        - Isley Brothers - The real deal, 1982; SR-26683; Isley Brothers (Box 40)
          Catalog # FZ 38047; A-side Matrix # G1 PAL-38047-F1
        - Isley Brothers - Go all the way, 1980; SR-26684; Isley Brothers (Box 40)
          Catalog # EPC 84025; A-side Matrix # 84025-A AL 36305-1B
          Epic
          Madrid, Spain
        - Isley Brothers - Grand slam, 1981; SR-26685; Isley Brothers (Box 40)
          Catalog # FZ 37080; A-side Matrix # PAL 37080-1G
        - Isley Brothers - Live it up, 1974; SR-26686; Isley Brothers (Box 40)
          Catalog # PZ 33070; A-side Matrix # AL-33070-1E
        - Isley Brothers - Grand slam, 1981; SR-26687; Isley Brothers (Box 40)
        - Isley Brothers - Get into something, 1969; SR-26688; Isley Brothers (Box 40)
          Catalog # TNS 3006; A-side Matrix # TNS 3006 A
        - Isley Brothers - Timeless (Disc one), 1978; SR-26689; Isley Brothers (Box 40)
          In same jacket as # SR-26690. Double album.
          Catalog # KZ2 35650; A-side Matrix # PAL 35651-1G
        - Isley Brothers - Timeless (Disc two), 1978; SR-26690; Isley Brothers (Box 40)
          In same jacket as # SR-26689. Double album.
          Catalog # KZ2 35650; A-side Matrix # AL-35652-1G
        - Isley Brothers - Between the sheets, 1983; SR-26691; Isley Brothers (Box 40)
          Catalog # FZ 38674; A-side Matrix # PAL-38674-1B
        - Isley Brothers - Masterpiece, 1985; SR-26692; Isley Brothers (Box 40)
          Catalog # 1-25347; A-side Matrix # 1-25347-A SR1
          Warner Bros. Records
        - Isley Brothers - Rockin' with fire, 1978; SR-26693; Isley Brothers (Box 40)
          In same jacket as # SR-26694. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 2Z8-2283; A-side Matrix # 2S8-2283-4-AA
        - Isley Brothers - Rockin' with fire, 1978; SR-26694; Isley Brothers (Box 40)
          In same jacket as # SR-26693. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 2Z8-2283; A-side Matrix # 2Z8-2283-4AA
        - Isley Brothers - Who said?, 1979; SR-26695; Isley Brothers (Box 40)
          Catalog # AS 893; A-side Matrix # XSS168415-1B
        - Isley Brothers - Hurry up and wait, 1981; SR-26696; Isley Brothers (Box 40)
          Catalog # AS 947; A-side Matrix # XSS168548-1B
        - It Spy - Have you got EP, 1996; SR-26697; It Spy (Box 40)
          In same jacket as # SR-26698. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SKINT 9; A-side Matrix # SKINT+9+B
          Skint
          Brighton, United Kingdom
        - It Spy - Have you got EP, 1996; SR-26698; It Spy (Box 40)
          In same jacket as # SR-26697. 2 copies.
        - J. Majik - Infrastructure (Disc one), 2001; SR-26699; J. Majik (Box 40)
          In same jacket as # SR-26700, SR-26701, SR-26702. Quadruple album.
          Catalog # INFRA003LP; A-side Matrix # INFRALP003 B
          Infrared
        - J. Majik - Infrastructure (Disc two), 2001; SR-26700; J. Majik (Box 40)
          In same jacket as # SR-26699, SR-26701, SR-26702. Quadruple album.
          Catalog # INFRA003LP; A-side Matrix # INFRALP003 D
        - J. Majik - Infrastructure (Disc three), 2001; SR-26701; J. Majik (Box 40)
          In same jacket as # SR-26699, SR-26700, SR-26702. Quadruple album.
          Catalog # INFRA003LP; A-side Matrix # INFRALP003 F
        - J. Majik - Infrastructure (Disc four), 2001; SR-26702; J. Majik (Box 40)
          In same jacket as # SR-26699, SR-26700, SR-26701. Quadruple album.
          Catalog # INFRA003LP; A-side Matrix # INFRALP003 H
        - Jabara, Paul - The third album, 1979; SR-26703; Jabara, Paul (Box 40)
          Catalog # NBLP 7163 DJ; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7163-AS-CP-2
          Casablanca
        - Jack Master Funk - Aw shucks (let's go let's go), 1985; SR-26704; Jack Master Funk (Box 40)
          Catalog # FU2; A-side Matrix # PRL 8542A
          House Records
          Chicago, Illinois
        - Jackson 5 - ABC, 1970; SR-26705; Jackson 5 (Box 40)
          Catalog # MS-709; A-side Matrix # HS-1718-3 Z4RS-2927-1
          Motown
        - Jackson 5 - Skywriter, 1973; SR-26706; Jackson 5 (Box 40)
          Catalog # M 761L; A-side Matrix # C5RS-7524-REI-03B 1306722-03B
        - Jackson, Chuck - When the fuel runs out, 1979; SR-26707; Jackson, Chuck (Box 40)
          Catalog # CD103D; A-side Matrix # CD-103MA
          Channel
        - Jackson, Chuck - Needing you, wanting you, 1975; SR-26708; Jackson, Chuck (Box 40)
          Catalog # AP-3014; A-side Matrix # AP-4024-GM
          All Platinum
          Englewood, New Jersey
        - Jackson, Dee D. - Thunder & lightning, 1980; SR-26709; Jackson, Dee D. (Box 40)
          Catalog # 202 089; A-side Matrix # 202089 A-1/80S
          Jupiter Records
          Munchen, Germany
        - J. J. Jackson's Dilemma - J.J. Jackson's Dilemma, 1970; SR-26710; J. J. Jackson's Dilemma; Jackson, J. J. (Box 40)
          Catalog # PLP 3; A-side Matrix # Z4RS-0291-1
          Perception Records
        - Jackson, Janet - Rhythm nation 1814, 1989; SR-26711; Jackson, Janet (Box 41)
          Catalog # SP-3920; A-side Matrix # SP-03920-A ES2
          A&M Records
          Santa Monica, California
        - Jackson, Janet - Rhythm nation, 1989; SR-26712; Jackson, Janet (Box 41)
          Catalog # SP-12335; A-side Matrix # A&M SP 012335 A ES1
        - Jackson, Janet - Alright, 1989; SR-26713; Jackson, Janet (Box 41)
          Catalog # SP-12351; A-side Matrix # A&M SP012351 A DMM
        - Jackson, Janet - Control, 1986; SR-26714; Jackson, Janet (Box 41)
          Catalog # SP-5106; A-side Matrix # SP0-5106-A-ES1
        - Jackson, Jermaine - Shake it up; Little girl don't you worry; you like me don't you, 1980; SR-26715; Jackson, Jermaine; Dazz Band (Box 41)
          In same jacket as # SR-26716. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PR 78; A-side Matrix # PR-78 (A)-66188-D15A ZXH
        - Jackson, Jermaine - Shake it up; Little girl don't you worry; you like me don't you, 1980; SR-26716; Jackson, Jermaine; Dazz Band (Box 41)
          In same jacket as # SR-26715. 2 copies.
        - Jackson, Jermaine - Let's get serious, 1980; SR-26717; Jackson, Jermaine (Box 41)
          Catalog # M7-928R1; A-side Matrix # M7-928-R1-Side A13B AKF
        - Jackson, Jermaine - Precious moments, 1986; SR-26718; Jackson, Jermaine (Box 41)
          Catalog # AL8-8277; A-side Matrix # AL8-8277-SA RCA2
          Arista
        - Jackson, Joe - Joe Jackson's jumpin' jive, 1981; SR-26719; Jackson, Joe (Box 41)
          Catalog # SP-4871; A-side Matrix # A&M SP-04871-A P2
        - Jackson, La Toya - La Toya Jackson, 1980; SR-26720; Jackson, La Toya (Box 41)
          In same jacket as # SR-26721. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PD-1-6291; A-side Matrix # PD-1-6291-A K
        - Jackson, La Toya - La Toya Jackson, 1980; SR-26721; Jackson, La Toya (Box 41)
          In same jacket as # SR-26720. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PD-1-6291; A-side Matrix # PD-1-6291-AS-SP1
        - Jackson, Michael - Cheeky choons (volume two), 2002; SR-26722; Jackson, Michael (Box 41)
          This pseudo-label is a holding area for all unofficial releases and bootlegs containing music by Michael Jackson where no proper or other label/company is discernible.
          Catalog # HEAD-2; A-side Matrix # HEADZ-2-A
          United Kingdom
        - Jacko - PYT (Pretty Young Thing), 2003; SR-26723; Jacko; Jackson, Michael; Lost Vegas (Box 41)
          Catalog # PLAY 005; A-side Matrix # PLAY 005 A1
          Playable Music
        - Jackson, Michael - Forever, Michael, 1975; SR-26724; Jackson, Michael (Box 41)
          Catalog # M6-825S1; A-side Matrix # M6-825S1-E5RS-7508-1 1-03A
        - Jackson, Michael - Off the wall, 1979; SR-26725; Jackson, Michael (Box 41)
          Catalog # FE 35745; A-side Matrix # PAL 35745-2D
        - Jackson, Michael - Invincible (Disc one), 2001; SR-26726; Jackson, Michael (Box 41)
          In same jacket as # SR-26727. Double album.
          Catalog # E2 69400; A-side Matrix # AL 86192-1A
        - Jackson, Michael - Invincible (Disc two), 2001; SR-26727; Jackson, Michael (Box 41)
          In same jacket as # SR-26726. Double album.
          Catalog # E2 69400; A-side Matrix # AL 86193-2A
        - Jackson, Michael - You are not alone, 1995; SR-26728; Jackson, Michael (Box 41)
          Catalog # 662310 6; A-side Matrix # 01 662310 20 1A1
        - Jackson, Michael - They don't care for us (Disc one), 1995; SR-26729; Jackson, Michael (Box 41)
          In same jacket as # SR-26730. Double album.
          Catalog # E2S 7770; A-side Matrix # XSS 7771B-1A
        - Jackson, Michael - They don't care for us (Disc two), 1995; SR-26730; Jackson, Michael (Box 41)
          In same jacket as # SR-26729. Double album.
          Catalog # E2S 7770; A-side Matrix # XSS 7772B-2A
        - Jackson, Michael Gregory - Heart & center, 1979; SR-26731; Jackson, Michael Gregory (Box 41)
          Catalog # AN 3015; A-side Matrix # AN-3015-SA-1
          Arista Novus
        - Jackson, Mick - Weekend, 1978; SR-26732; Jackson, Mick (Box 41)
          Catalog # DSKO 141; A-side Matrix # ST-DSKO-36269-3
        - Jackson, Millie - For men only, 1980; SR-26733; Jackson, Millie (Box 41)
          Catalog # SP-1-6727; A-side Matrix # SP-1-6727-AS
          Spring Records
        - Jackson, Millie - Live and uncensored (Disc one), 1979; SR-26734; Jackson, Millie (Box 41)
          In same jacket as # SR-26735. Double album.
          Catalog # SP-2-6725; A-side Matrix # SP-2-6725-AS-K